Joanne Alter Paper
University of Illinois at Chicago
- Series III: Metropolitan Sanitary District Subject Files
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 326)
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 327)
  - C - Constituent Inquiries, 1974-1989 (Box 42, Folder 328)
  - Des Plaines Diversion Project, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 329)
  - D - Miscellaneous, 1973-1989 (Box 43, Folder 330)
  - D - Constituent Inquiries, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 331)
  - Energy, 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 332)
  - Energy Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 333)
  - Energy - Biomass, 1979-1989 (Box 43, Folder 334)
  - Energy, 1975-1990 (Box 43, Folder 335)
  - Energy - Biomass, 1979-1989 (Box 44, Folder 336)
  - Energy, 1973-1979 (Box 44, Folder 337)
  - Energy - ComEd, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 338)
  - Energy - ComEd, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 339)
  - Energy - Gasohol, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 340)
  - Energy - Gasohol News 1979-1981 (Box 45, Folder 341)
  - Energy - Methane, 1975-1984 (Box 45, Folder 342)
  - Energy - Nuclear, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 343)
  - Engineering Consultants, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 344)
  - Engineering Consultants, 1973-1987 (Box 46, Folder 345)
  - E- Constituent Inquiries, 1979-1986 (Box 46, Folder 346)
  - Flood Control, 1979-1989 (Box 46, Folder 347)
  - Flood Control, 1979-1989 (Box 46, Folder 348)
  - Flood Control, 1979-1985 (Box 46, Folder 349)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1974-1980 (Box 47, Folder 350)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1973-1983 (Box 47, Folder 351)
  - Flood Control, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 352)
  - Flood Control, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 353)
  - Flood Control - Arlington Heights, 1984-1988 (Box 48, Folder 354)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 355)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1982-1989 (Box 48, Folder 356)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 357)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 358)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 359)
  - Friends of the Chicago River, 1980-1989 (Box 49, Folder 360)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Chicago Aquatic Center, 1982-1985 (Box 49, Folder 361)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Steering Committee Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 49, Folder 362)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Steering Committee Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 49, Folder 363)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Steering Committee Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 364)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Newsclips, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 365)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Newsclips, 1983-1987 (Box 50, Folder 366)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Newsclips, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 367)
  - Friends of the Parks, 1977-1990 (Box 50, Folder 368)
  - Fulton County, 1977-1987 (Box 50, Folder 369)
  - Fulton County, 1977-1987 (Box 50, Folder 370)
  - Friends of the Chicago River - Steering Committee Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 51, Folder 371)
  - Hoffman Estates, 1981-1986 (Box 51, Folder 372)
  - Hoffman Estates, 1981-1986 (Box 51, Folder 373)
  - G-H - Miscellaneous, 1980-1988 (Box 51, Folder 374)
  - F-H Constituent Inquiries, 1976-1987 (Box 52, Folder 375)
  - F-H Constituent Inquiries, 1976-1987 (Box 52, Folder 376)
  - Industrial Work, 1984-1990 (Box 52, Folder 377)
  - I - Miscellaneous, 1974-1984 (Box 52, Folder 378)
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 379)
  - I-K Constituent Inquiries, 1978-1987 (Box 52, Folder 380)
  - Lake Diversion, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 381)
  - Lake Michigan, 1986-1989 (Box 52, Folder 382)
  - Lake Michigan, 1986-1989 (Box 53, Folder 383)
  - Lake Water, 1981-1985 (Box 53, Folder 384)
  - Land Use, 1977-1983 (Box 53, Folder 385)
  - Land Use, 1980-1989 (Box 53, Folder 386)
  - Land Use, 1980-1989 (Box 53, Folder 387)
  - Land Use, 1974-1986 (Box 54, Folder 388)
  - Land Use, 1983-1989 (Box 54, Folder 389)
  - Land Use, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 390)
  - Land Use - Heritage Corridor, 1977-1986 (Box 54, Folder 391)
  - Land Use - Legal, 1974-1984 (Box 54, Folder 392)
  - Land Use - North Avenue Turning Basin, 1984-1989 (Box 54, Folder 393)
  - Land Use - North Shore, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 394)
  - Land Use - North Shore, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 395)
  - Land Use - North Shore, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 396)
  - Land Use - North Shore, 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 397)
  - Land Use - Riveredge Renaissance, 1983-1989 (Box 55, Folder 398)
  - Land Use, 1976-1984 (Box 55, Folder 399)
  - Land Use, 1974-1977 (Box 56, Folder 400)
  - Land Use Hearings - Bremmen and McCook, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 401)
  - Land Use Hearings - Bdroom and Evanston, 1976-1979 (Box 56, Folder 402)
  - Lucas Berg Pit, 1973-1986 (Box 56, Folder 403)
  - L - Constituent Inquiries, 1973-1990 (Box 56, Folder 404)
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1981-1988 (Box 56, Folder 405)
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1979-1987 (Box 57, Folder 406)
  - Land Reclamation, 1973-1979 (Box 57, Folder 407)
  - Land Reclamation, 1964-1977 (Box 57, Folder 408)
  - Land Reclamation - Metals, 1973-1979 (Box 57, Folder 409)
  - Land Reclamation - Reports, 1977-1982 (Box 57, Folder 410)
  - Land Reclamation - Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 57, Folder 411)
  - Land Reclamation - University of Illinois, 1979-1992 (Box 58, Folder 412)
  - MSD - Miscellaneous, 1976-1987 (Box 58, Folder 413)
  - M - Constituent Inquiries, 1973-1988 (Box 58, Folder 414)
  - Northeastern Illinois Planning Commission, 1987-1990 (Box 58, Folder 415)
  - Northeastern Illinois Planning Commission, 1985-1990 (Box 58, Folder 416)
  - Northeastern Illinois Planning Commission, 1984-1987 (Box 59, Folder 417)
  - Northeastern Illinois Planning Commission, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 418)
  - Northeastern Illinois Planning Commission, 1987-1989 (Box 59, Folder 419)
  - N - Miscellaneous, 1982-1986 (Box 59, Folder 420)
  - N - Constituent Inquiries, 1975-1989 (Box 59, Folder 421)
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1985-1990 (Box 59, Folder 422)
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1977-1988 (Box 59, Folder 423)
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1978-1985 (Box 60, Folder 424)
  - O - Citizen Inquiries, 1976-1987 (Box 60, Folder 425)
  - Personnel - General, 1979-1990 (Box 60, Folder 426)
  - Personnel - General, 1977-1986 (Box 60, Folder 427)
  - Personnel - General, 1978-1983 (Box 60, Folder 428)
  - Personnel - General, 1980-1986 (Box 60, Folder 429)
  - Personnel - General, 1974-1983 (Box 60, Folder 430)
  - Personnel - Exams, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 431)
  - Personnel - Exams, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 432)
  - Personnel - Insurance, 1975-1984 (Box 61, Folder 433)
  - Personnel - Job Requests, 1984-1988 (Box 61, Folder 434)
  - Personnel - Job Requests, 1977-1985 (Box 61, Folder 435)
  - Personnel - Pension, 1979-1987 (Box 62, Folder 436)
  - Pesticides, 1979-1987 (Box 62, Folder 437)
  - Pesticides, 1978-1983 (Box 62, Folder 438)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1977-1983 (Box 62, Folder 439)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1975-1986 (Box 62, Folder 440)
  - P - Constituent Inquiries, 1973-1987 (Box 63, Folder 441)
  - Real Estate, 1981-1987 (Box 63, Folder 442)
  - Real Estate, 1985-1990 (Box 63, Folder 443)
  - P-R - Miscellaneous, 1976-1989 (Box 63, Folder 444)
  - P-R - Miscellaneous, 1975-1990 (Box 63, Folder 445)
  - R - Constituent Inquiries, 1974-1989 (Box 63, Folder 446)
  - Solids Disposal, 1986-1989 (Box 63, Folder 447)
  - Solids Disposal, 1976-1988 (Box 64, Folder 448)
  - Solids Disposal, 1975-1988 (Box 64, Folder 449)
  - Solids Disposal, 1982-1989 (Box 64, Folder 450)
  - Solids Disposal, 1980-1986 (Box 64, Folder 451)
  - Speeches - JHA, 1973-1985 (Box 64, Folder 452)
  - Speeches - JHA [photos], 1985-1990 (Box 65, Folder 453)
  - Speeches - JHA, 1985-1990 (Box 65, Folder 454)
  - Student Term Papers, 1977-1987 (Box 65, Folder 455)
  - STU - Miscellaneous, 1975-1986 (Box 65, Folder 456)
  - STU - Miscellaneous, 1975-1986 (Box 65, Folder 457)
  - Toxics [photos], 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 458)
  - S - Constituent Inquiries, 1974-1989 (Box 66, Folder 459)
  - Toxics, 1984-1988 (Box 66, Folder 460)
  - Toxics - Groundwater, 1984-1988 (Box 66, Folder 461)
  - Treasurer, 1981-1988 (Box 67, Folder 462)
  - T - Constituent Inquiries, 1973-1989 (Box 67, Folder 463)
  - UVW - Miscellaneous, 1985-1988 (Box 67, Folder 464)
  - UVW - Miscellaneous, 1976-1988 (Box 67, Folder 465)
  - UVW - Miscellaneous, 1983-1990 (Box 67, Folder 466)
  - WYZ - Constituent Inquiries, 1974-1987 (Box 67, Folder 467)
- Series IV: Democratic Party and Affiliates
  - Scope and Content Note: This series contains materials pertaining to Democratic Party events, organizational affiliates, and candidates.
  - Center for National Policy, 1981-1987 (Box 68, Folder 468)
  - Center for National Policy - Publications, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 469)
  - Democratic State Central Committee, 1985-1990 (Box 68, Folder 470)
  - Democratic Policy Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 471)
  - Democratic Policy Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 472)
  - Democratic National Convention - Appointment, 1976-1985 (Box 68, Folder 473)
  - Democratic National Convention - Platform Accountability Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 68, Folder 474)
  - Democratic National Convention - Delegate Selection, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 475)
  - Democratic National Convention - Charter and Bylaws, 1980-1988 (Box 69, Folder 476)
  - Democratic National Convention - Women, 1983-1987 (Box 69, Folder 477)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 478)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 479)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 480)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1985-1986 (Box 70, Folder 481)
  - Paul Simon for President, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 482)
  - 1988 Presidential Candidates, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 483)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 484)
  - Dukakis Campaign, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 485)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 486)
  - Democratic National Convention - Papers, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 487)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 488)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 489)
- Series V: Alter Organizational Work
  - Scope and Content Note: This series contains materials pertaining to volunteer and trustee work undertaken by Alter.
  - Chicago Access Corporation, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 490)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 491)
  - Art Institute, 1986-1990 (Box 73, Folder 492)
  - Art Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 73, Folder 493)
  - A - Miscellaneous, 1981-1989 (Box 73, Folder 494)
  - Biography - Who's Who entry, 1980-1986 (Box 73, Folder 495)
  - Bork - Judicial Candidate, 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 496)
  - Bright New City, 1987-1990 (Box 73, Folder 497)
  - B - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 74, Folder 498)
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Box 74, Folder 499)
  - Democratic Women's Candidates, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 500)
  - ERA - Correspondence, 1972-1989 (Box 74, Folder 501)
  - ERA - Organizations, 1973-1989 (Box 74, Folder 502)
  - ERA, 1967-1980 (Box 74, Folder 503)
  - Ethics - Political, 1973-1986 (Box 74, Folder 504)
  - Hartigan - Gubernatorial Candidate, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 505)
  - Illinois Democratic Women's Caucus, 1973-1987 (Box 74, Folder 506)
  - International Women's Year, 1975-1985 (Box 75, Folder 507)
  - I - Miscellaneous, 1982-1990 (Box 75, Folder 508)
  - J - Miscellaneous, 1985-1989 (Box 75, Folder 509)
  - Midwest Women's Center, 1987-1991 (Box 75, Folder 510)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1985-1989 (Box 75, Folder 511)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Friends of Art, 1980-1981 (Box 75, Folder 512)
  - Merit Selection of Judges, 1977-1987 (Box 75, Folder 513)
  - Midwest Women's Center, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 514)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1985-1989 (Box 76, Folder 515)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Art Advisory Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 76, Folder 516)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Art Advisory Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 76, Folder 517)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Art Advisory Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 518)
  - Recommendations, 1974-1990 (Box 77, Folder 519)
  - Recommendations, 1976-1981 (Box 77, Folder 520)
  - R - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 521)
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 522)
  - Townsend, Kathleen - Campaign, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 523)
  - Sierra Club, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 524)
  - Squeaky Wheel, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 525)
  - M-N - Miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Box 77, Folder 526)
  - Women, 1974-1988 (Box 77, Folder 527)
  - YWCA - Leadership Luncheon, 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 528)
  - Women's Committee - World's Fair, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 529)
  - Women, 1984-1990 (Box 78, Folder 530)
  - Women, 1984-1989 (Box 78, Folder 531)
- Series VI: Tunnel and Reservoir Plan (TARP)
  - Scope and Content Note: This series contains materials from the Metropolitan Sanitation District project to address combined sewer overflows.
  - TARP, 1976-1989 (Box 79, Folder 532)
  - TARP, 1978-1981 (Box 79, Folder 533)
  - TARP - JHA Position Statement, 1978-1989 (Box 79, Folder 534)
  - TARP, 1977-1986 (Box 79, Folder 535)
  - TARP, 1974-1989 (Box 79, Folder 536)
  - TARP, 1986-1990 (Box 80, Folder 537)
  - TARP, 1986-1988 (Box 80, Folder 538)
  - TARP - Blasting Complaints [photos], 1977-1986 (Box 80, Folder 539)
  - TARP - Blasting Complaints, 1975-1986 (Box 80, Folder 540)
  - TARP - Anti-TARP groups, 1976-1981 (Box 81, Folder 541)
  - TARP - Anti-TARP groups, 1977-1981 (Box 81, Folder 542)
  - TARP - Anti-TARP groups, 1977-1979 (Box 81, Folder 543)
  - TARP - General Accounting Office Report, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 544)
  - TARP - General Accounting Office Report, 1979-1987 (Box 81, Folder 545)
  - TARP - General Accounting Office Report, 1975-1981 (Box 82, Folder 546)
  - TARP - General Accounting Office Report, 1978-1981 (Box 82, Folder 547)
  - TARP - General Accounting Office Report, 1979-1981 (Box 82, Folder 548)
  - TARP - Data, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 549)
  - TARP - Data, 1976-1990 (Box 82, Folder 550)
  - TARP - Data, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 551)
  - TARP - Data, 1977-1982 (Box 83, Folder 552)
  - TARP - EPA, 1974-1982 (Box 83, Folder 553)
  - TARP - EPA, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 554)
  - TARP - John Gnaedinger, 1976-1982 (Box 83, Folder 555)
  - TARP - Hydrogen Sulfide, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 556)
  - TARP - Local Sewers, 1974-1978 (Box 84, Folder 557)
  - TARP - NAS and BRAB, 1974-1979 (Box 84, Folder 558)
  - TARP - Insurance, 1977-1987 (Box 84, Folder 559)
  - TARP - Army Corps of Engineers, 1976-1982 (Box 84, Folder 560)
  - TARP - Government Agencies, 1975-1978 (Box 85, Folder 561)
  - TARP - Government Agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 85, Folder 562)
  - TARP - Rock Controversy, 1977-1990 (Box 85, Folder 563)
  - TARP - Rock Controversy, 1976-1982 (Box 85, Folder 564)
  - TARP - Rock Storage, 1979-1988 (Box 85, Folder 565)
  - TARP - Rock Storage, 1982-1984 (Box 85, Folder 566)
  - TARP - Rock Report, 1981-1988 (Box 86, Folder 567)
  - TARP - Rock Bids, 1978-1989 (Box 86, Folder 568)
  - TARP - Rock Bids, 1981-1984 (Box 86, Folder 569)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 570)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 571)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 572)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 573)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 574)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 575)
  - TARP - Safety, 1987-1989 (Box 87, Folder 576)
  - TARP - Press Coverage, 1983-1990 (Box 88, Folder 577)
  - TARP - Press Coverage, 1981-1986 (Box 88, Folder 578)
- Series VII: Alter Career Miscellaneous
  - Scope and Content Note: This series contains various career subject files, and are kept separate to reflect the order of Alter's own files.
  - Speeches, 1974-1983 (Box 88, Folder 579)
  - Speeches, 1972-1985 (Box 88, Folder 580)
  - Centennial Fountain, 1982-1990 (Box 89, Folder 581)
  - Centennial Fountain, 1986-1989 (Box 89, Folder 582)
  - Centennial Fountain - Fundraising, 1987-1988 (Box 89, Folder 583)
  - Centennial Fountain - Fundraising, 1987-1988 (Box 89, Folder 584)
  - Centennial Fountain, 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 585)
  - Centennial Fountain - Sculptors [photos and negatives], 1986 (Box 90, Folder 586)
  - Centennial Fountain - Sculptors [photos and negatives], 1981-1987 (Box 90, Folder 587)
  - Centennial Fountain - Sculptors [photos and negatives], 1986 (Box 90, Folder 588)
  - Centennial Fountain - Sculptors [photos and negatives], 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 589)
  - County Clerk Campaign, 1989-1990 (Box 90, Folder 590)
- Series VIII: Oversized Items
  - Scrapbook and Miscellaneous Campaign Paraphernalia, undated (Box 91, Folder 0)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 92, Folder 0)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 93, Folder 0)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 94, Folder 0)
  - Campaign Apparel and Posters, undated (Box 95, Folder 0)